odule.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who was the last emperor of the Western Roman Empire?',
    a: 'Augustulus',
    b: 'Nero',
    c: 'Julius Caeser',
    d: 'Titus',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What animal is fastest?',
    a: 'Peregrine Falcon',
    b: 'Cheetah',
    c: 'Lion',
    d: 'Sail Fish',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these films was NOT nominated for Best Picture?',
    a: 'Eighth Grade',
    b: 'Black Panther',
    c: 'Vice',
    d: 'Bohemian Rhapsody',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many sides does a icosahedron have?',
    a: '16',
    b: '20',
    c: '12',
    d: '24',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the most popular dog breed?',
    a: 'German Shepard',
    b: 'Golden Retrievers',
    c: 'Bulldog',
    d: 'Labradors',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Stratocaster is made by which guitar brand?',
    a: 'Les Paul',
    b: 'Gibson',
    c: 'Fender',
    d: 'Taylor',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What show has been running for more seasons?',
    a: 'Greys Anatomy',
    b: 'Supernatural',
    c: 'Its Always Sunny in Philadelphia',
    d: 'The Bachelorette',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the oldest soda?',
    a: 'Dr. Pepper',
    b: 'Coca Cola',
    c: 'Root Beer',
    d: 'Pepsi',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In Star Trek: TNG, what was the name of Datas twin brother?',
    a: 'Set',
    b: 'Soong',
    c: 'Lore',
    d: 'Mode',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT an original Starbursts color?',
    a: 'Pink',
    b: 'Green',
    c: 'Red',
    d: 'Orange',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];